Fahmi Ali Husni

Panyuwangi, East Java, Indonesia

✓ fahmiali130499@gmail.com

\$\cdot+6282131715623 \quad \text{in} https://www.linkedin.com/in/fahmialihusni/

SUMMARY

Experienced in web developer, especially in frontend and ui/ux designer. I am currently continuing my 8th semester of Informatics majoring at the University of Muhammadiyah Malang and have a passion for development and technology such as coding, research, and competitive programming.

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Engineering Intern

PT. Singhasari SEZ - SEAL

July 2022 - December 2022, Malang, Indonesia

February 2022 - July 2022, Jakarta, Indonesia

- I am using the Next.JS framework with the Typescript programming language
- Slicing the UI design into the website
- Using the CSS framework with TailwindCSS and UI Components with Flowbite
- · State management with Redux
- Using the Fetching API with Axios
- Progress management with Trello

Frontend Engineering Student - KAMPUS MERDEKA YABB & GoTo

- · I learned FrontEnd by using ReactJs
- · Create Spotify playlists using Spotify Developer with React technology using TypeScript language
- Implementing UI components using react components, such as react bootstrap and implementing styling tailwind css
- · Spotify playlist can search songs, create, edit and delete playlists

Input Data for Covid-19 Vaccine Student Events

UIN Maulana Malik Ibrahim Malang

• Vaccine data input

September 2021, Malang, Indonesia

React JS for Web Development

Digital Talent Scholarship - KOMINFO

- · Make a website calculator
- · Create a to-do list website

May 2022 - 25 June 2022, Indonesia

ORGANIZATION

Informatics Student Association

University of Muhammadiyah Malang Informatics

• Information & Communication (INFOKOM)

February 2022 - July 2022, Malang, Indonesia

EDUCATION

University of Muhammadiyah Malang

Informatics Engineering

• Software Engineering

September 2019 - Present

PROJECT

Web Developer

- WordPress Personal Blog (www.projectfa.com)
- FAL Food Store (https://fal-store.netlify.app/)
- MyPortfolio (https://fahmiali.netlify.app/)
- Web Fullstack Service(http://widduserviceeee.herokuapp.com/)
- Web Design Competetion HimitPens Surabaya (https://botnet-web.netlify.app/)
- Web School Company Profile and Registation Online in Elementary 1 Watukebo (https://sdn1watukebo.sch.id/)
- $\bullet \ Calculator \ Website \ (https://fahmiali99.github.io/calculator.github.io/)$
- Leaf Classification (https://image-klasifikasi-daun.herokuapp.com/)
- Spotify Playlist (https://fal-music.vercel.app/)
- SIPP Kota Batu (https://sipp-dev.vercel.app/)
- Spotify Clone (https://github.com/Fahmiali99/Spotify)

September 2019 - Present

UI / UX Design October 2019 - Present

- YGuide App Mobile
- Ambul App Mobile
- Booklogia Web App
- Botnet Web App
- Widdu Service Web App

SKILLS

Programming Language: PHP, Java, C++, C, Python, Javascript,

TypeScript, Dart

Framework : Webpack, Laravel, ReactJs, NextJs, AngularJs, Flutter

Styling: Bootstrap, Tailwind Css

UI Component : React Bootstrap, Chakra, Material UI

Design Photo: Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Figma, Adobe XD

Video Editing: Adobe Premiere Pro, Vegas, Filmora

Audio Editing: Cubase 5, FL Studio, Pro Tools